

NITIPOOM G\$NGFU

"I will apply my abilities to complete the assigned tasks and am ready to learn new things from the workplace. I am prepared to handle pressure and work as part of a team, as well as gain valuable work experience to the best of my ability."

CONTACT



(+66) 081-907 7307



s6603052421160@email.kmutnb.ac.th



118/3-9 soi Wat Matchantikaram Wong Sawang, Bang Sue, Bangkok 18100

LANGUAGE

• Thai: Native speaker

• English : Basic

SKILLS & ABILITIES

- Microsoft Word
- Microsoft Excel
- MicrosoftPowerpoint
- Adobe Photoshop
- C, C+, C#
- Java, Javascript
- HTML, php
- CSS
- Fluter
- Python

PERSONAL QUALITIES

- Team oriented
- Learn new things
- Responssibillity

EDUCATION

2023-present

Bachelor of Industrial Technology in Electronice Technology Computer from King Mongkut 's University of Technology North Bangkok, Bangkok, GPAX : 3.12

2021-2022

Hing Vocational Certificate geaduate in Information Technology form Saraburi Technical College, Saraburi, GPAX : 3.39

2018-2020

Vocational Certificate geaduate in Information Technology form Saraburi Technical College, Saraburi. GPAX: 3.18

WORK EXPERIENCE

Student Trainee

October 2022 - June 2023

Trainee at Maxion Wheels(Thailand) co., ltd

Assistant IT Support Engineering

May 2020 - August 2020

Trainee at Saraburi Watchakit co.ltd

Assistant IT Support Engineering

FOR INTERNSHIP